Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art Board of Trustees records, 1869-2012 COR0001.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran Gallery of Art board of Trustees records
1869-2012
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Corcoran Gallery of Art
COR0001.0.RG
34.5 Linear Feet
In 1869, W.W. Corcoran formed the Board of Trustees for the Corcoran Gallery of Art. In 1874, the first Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees was held, and the Corcoran Gallery of Art opened to the public. The Trustees were responsible for the appointment of a director, the appropriation of funds, approval or rejection of art works, the maintenance of the building, approval of departmental reports, and other pertinent issues and events. The records consist of the minutes, agendas, and committee reports of quarterly, special, and annual meetings of the Trustees. The records date from 1869 to 2012.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open to research.
The records of the Board of Trustees are closed for 25 years from the date of creation.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The Corcoran Institution Board of Trustees donated these records to The George Washington University in 2016.
Arrangement
Organized into 3 series: Early meeting records; Records transferred post-1980; and Early meeting ledgers.
Historical narrative
The first section of this history, covering events through 1981, was prepared by Corcoran Archivist Katherine M. Kovocs for publication in 1985 with the support of the National Endowment for the Humanities.
In 1869, W.W. Corcoran formed the Board of Trustees for the Corcoran Gallery of Art. W.W. Corcoran submitted a deed stating the Board's duties:
1. organization and foundation of a permanent Board of Trustees which may make, alter, amend, repeal, re-enact the by-laws, rules and regulations
2. consistently forming a board of nine members replenishing when the need arises
3. accounting for and maintaining the property, rights and credits of the Gallery
4. establishment and maintenance of a public gallery for the promotion and encouragement of the arts of painting and sculpture, and fine arts with merits set by the Trustees
5. management of the Board of Trustees as they see fit
6. control the works of art donated to the Gallery, accepting or declining as they see fit
7. maintenance of the Gallery as specified by W.W. Corcoran; however, if the Board of Trustees makes a major breach of contract, the contract will be void
8. application for an Act of Congress if the need arises.
In 1874, the first Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees was held, and the Corcoran Gallery of Art opened to the public. The Board consisted of nine members with a President, Vice President, Secretary, Treasurer, and Curator. In 1900, the by-laws were amended changing the position of Curator to Director. In 1931, the by-laws were again amended creating the position of Second Vice President. The by-laws state that the Board will meet four times a year- January, April, June and October with an Annual Meeting the third Monday of January. The by-laws state the various committees with their individual duties: Committee on the Building, Committee on Works of Art, Committee on Accounts, and Committee on Legislation. The by-laws were amended in 1937, changing the Committee on Works of Art to Committee on Works of Art and the School. The by-laws were amended again in 1949 creating a new Executive Committee to continue the functions of the Board of Trustees on a regular basis. Many of these amendments reflect the growth and development of the institution.
The major purpose of the Board of Trustees is to oversee the management and development of the Gallery and School. It is significant that these nine members of the Board have worked as a unit for the Corcoran's betterment. Since the Board forms the major controlling network of the Corcoran, it is constantly involved with major and minor decisions. The Board has made four major decisions affecting the Corcoran Gallery of Art's direction:
1. the decision to sell the Renwick and build a new (present) building
2. the decision to accept the Clark Bequest constructing the addition to house the Clark Collection and expanding the Museum as a whole
3. the decision that every thirty years the Board renews the Gallery's policies through an updated statement of W.W. Corcoran's ideas
4. the decision to seek degree granting authority and accreditation for the Corcoran School of Art.
In 1968, in an effort to broaden the Gallery's base of support, the Board of Governors was formed to assist the Board of Trustees. In 1973, the Board of Governors was disbanded and the Board of Trustees was expanded beyond the original nine Life Trustees with the election of Term Trustees.
The following section of this history was prepared in 2019 by George Washington University SCRC staff with the support of the Luce Foundation.
The nine Life Trustees were exempt from annual re-elections, while the Term Trustees served two year terms subject to re-election. There would eventually be over sixty Term Trustees, leading to concerns about the size of the board, as well as divisions caused by the two-tiered system.
The Board of Trustees was reorganized in 1990 in response to the cancellation of the Robert Mapplethorpe exhibition "The Perfect Moment" in 1989. Life Trustees were abolished, and the by-laws were restructured in order to reduce the size of the Board of Trustees. A structured term and a rotation system for members of the Board was also introduced, as well as a more democratic system for nominating officers on the Board. The Board of Trustees adopted a new Statement of Purpose in 1993 as the final stage in an overall course correction for the Gallery.
In 1997, the Board of Trustees approved the resolution to use the 17th and New York Avenue NW plot to build an expansion to the Corcoran museum. By 2005 it had become clear that the Gallery would not be able to meet the financial obligations required, and the Board of Trustees suspended the plans for the expansion.
In 2013, faced with continuing financial hardship, the Board of Trustees began to explore a partnership with the University of Maryland. Concerns over the specifics of the proposed deal led the Trustees to decide, in May 2014, to instead work with the National Gallery of Art and George Washington University. The proposed plan would split the Gallery's collection and the School of Art between the National Gallery of Art and George Washington University, respectively, with George Washington University retaining ownership of the Flagg building.
Because the planned partition would violate the Gallery's deed of trust, the Trustees filed a petition with the District of Columbia for a court order allowing the trust to be broken under the doctrine of cy pres. The Court approved the petition, despite a counter petition from the Save the Corcoran group opposing the partition of the Gallery.
In 2018, as part of the agreement with the National Gallery of Art, the Corcoran Board of Trustees announced that 10,862 works of art would be freely distributed to museums in D.C. and around the country, with 99+% or 10,753 works, remaining in Washington D.C., and 8,631 pieces going to the NGA specifically.
Custodial History
The material in Series 1 Early Meeting records, 1869-1980 was transferred to the Corcoran Archives from various offices throughout the Gallery during the Archives initial processing project starting in January 1980. Records in Series 1 were accessioned by Brece V. Honeycutt.
Related Materials
Records for Trustee Committees overseeing a particular department, e.g., Education Committee, are housed with that Department's records.
Scope and Contents
The Board of Trustees records reflect the Corcoran Gallery of Art's growth and changes from 1869-2012. The records consist of the minutes, agendas, and committee reports of quarterly, special, and annual meetings of the Trustees. The Trustees were responsible for the appointment of a director, the appropriation of funds, approval or rejection of art works, the maintenance of the building, approval of departmental reports, and other pertinent issues and events. The records date from 1869 to 2012.
Art; Artists; Museums; Washington (D.C.)
- Early meeting records, 1869-1980; Series 1
  Arrangement
  Arranged chronologically.
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Meeting Minutes and Reports for the Board of Trustees from 1869-1980, covering the founding years of the Corcoran, development of the administration, and changes in internal structure of the institution.
  The reports of Trustees consist of individual committee and departmental reports. The curators' reports give an overall report on the Gallery. If the curator/director's report does mention an action, the committee reports may document the event. The Report of the Committee on Works of Art reports on: 1. works of art accessioned; 2. works of art repaired; 3, works of art deaccessioned; 4. specific donors; 5. after 1937, the actions of the Corcoran School of Art. The Committee on the Building reports on any repairs to the building, additions to the building, and bids and figures for the additions and repairs. The Committee on Finance and the Treasurer's report reflect the financial condition of the Gallery. Included are building fund reports, endowment fund reports and budget records. After 1956 records of the Committee on Membership appear. These records discuss the financial needs and programs for development and increased membership. After 1952 the Report of the Women's Committee appears, telling of reasons for their founding and of their activities and actions. After 1949 the reports of the Executive Committee appear. The Executive Committee was established to deal with the functions of the Gallery in between quarterly meetings.
  Related Materials
  Records of the Board of Trustees Meetings from 1869-1952 are also located in bound ledgers in Series 3 Early meeting ledgers, 1869-1952.
  - Report of Committee, 1869; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - First Annual Report, 1872-1874; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Second Annual Meeting Reports of Committees and Other Reports, 1874; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Second Annual Report, 1875; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Third Annual Report, 1876; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Reports, 1877; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Reports, 1978; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Reports, 1879; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Reports, 1800; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Reports, 1881; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Reports, 1882; Series 1 (Box 1, Folders 11-12)
  - Reports, 1883; Series 1 (Box 1, Folders 13-14)
  - Reports, 1884; Series 1 (Box 1, Folders 15-16)
  - Reports, 1885; Series 1 (Box 1, Folders 17-18)
  - Reports, 1886; Series 1 (Box 1, Folders 19-20)
  - Reports, 1887; Series 1 (Box 1, Folders 21-22)
  - Reports, 1888; Series 1 (Box 1, Folders 23-25)
  - Reports, 1889; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Reports, 1890; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Reports, 1891; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Reports, 1892; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Special Meeting, 1892 February 29; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Quartly Report, 1892 April 11; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1892 June; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1892 October 10; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Annual Meeting, 1893 January 9; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1893 April 10; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Quarterly Report, 1893 June 7; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Special Meeting, 1893 June 23; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Reports, 1893 July 8; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Quarterly Report, 1893 October 9; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Annual Meeting, 1894 January 15; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Quarterly Report, 1894 April 16; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Annual Meeting, 1894 June 18; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Quarterly Report, 1894 October 15; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Annual Meeting, 1895 January 28; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1895 April 19; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1895 June 17; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1895 October 21; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Annual Meeting, 1896 January 20; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Meeting, 1896 April 20; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1896 June 15; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1896 October 12; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Annual Meeting, 1897 January 18; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1897 April 25; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1897 June 12; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1897 October 18; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Annual Meeting, 1898 January 17; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Meeting, 1898 January 25; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Meeting, 1898 February 14; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Meeting, 1898 Febrary 24; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1898 April 18; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Semi-Annual Meeting, 1898 June 12; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1898 October 17; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Annual Meeting, 1899 January 17; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1899 April 5; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Meeting, 1899 April 17; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Special Meeting, 1899 April 19; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Special Meeting, 1899 April 24; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Quarterly Report, 1899 June 24; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1899 October 16; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Special Meeting, 1899 October 27; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Special Meeting, 1899 November 23; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Special Meeting, 1899 Dec 8; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Annual Meeting, 1900 January 15; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Special Meeting, 1900 February 8-March 30; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1900 April 16; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 1)
  - Special Meeting, 1900 April 18; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 2)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1900 June 18; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 3)
  - Special Meeting, 1900 June 26; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 4)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1900 October 15; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 5)
  - Annual Meeting, 1901 January 21; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 6)
  - Special Meeting, 1901 January 31; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 7)
  - Special Meeting, 1901 March 8; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 8)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1901 June 17; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 9)
  - Special Meeting, 1901 October 8; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 10)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1901 October 21; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 11)
  - Special Meeting, 1901 September 18; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 12)
  - Special Meeting, 1902 January 7, February 25; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 13)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1902 April 21; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 14)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1902 June 16; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 15)
  - Special Meeting, 1902 June 26; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 16)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1902 October 20; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 17)
  - Annual Meeting, 1903 January 1; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 18)
  - Annual Meeting, 1903 January 22; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 19)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1903 April 20; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 20)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1903 June 15; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 21)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1903 October 19, October 29; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 22)
  - Annual Meeting, 1904 January 18; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 23)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1904 April 18; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 24)
  - Special Meeting, 1904 June 16; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 25)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1904 June 20; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 26)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1904 October 17; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 27)
  - Special Meeting, 1904 November 5; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 28)
  - Annual Meeting, 1905 January 16; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 29)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1905 April 17; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 30)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1905 October 16; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 31)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1905 June 19; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 32)
  - Special Meeting, 1905 December 6; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 33)
  - Annual Meeting, 1906 January 15; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 34)
  - Special Meeting, 1906 March 16-28; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 35)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1906 April 16; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 36)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1906 June 18; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 37)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1906 October 15; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 38)
  - Annual Meeting, 1907 January 21; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 39)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1907 April 15; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 40)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1907 June 17; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 41)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1907 October 21; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 42)
  - Annual Meeting, 1908 January 20; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 43)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1908 April 20; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 44)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1908 June 15; Series 1 (Box 4A, Folder 45)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1908 October 19; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 1)
  - Special Meeting, 1908 December 4; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 2)
  - Annual Meeting, 1909 January 18; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 3)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1909 April 19; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 4)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1909 June 14; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 5)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1909 October 18; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 6)
  - Special Meeting, 1909 November 30, December 18; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting, 1910 January 17; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 8)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1910 April 18; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 9)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1910 June 20; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 10)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1910 October 17; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 11)
  - Special Meeting, 1910 December 5; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 12)
  - Annual Meeting, 1911 January 16; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 13)
  - Annual Meeting, 1911 January 16; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 14)
  - Special Meeting, 1911 March 9; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 15)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1911 April 17; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 16)
  - Special Meeting, 1911 May 1-18; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 17)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1911 June 19; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 18)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1911 October 16; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 19)
  - Annual Meeting, 1912 January 15; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 20)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1912 April 15; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 21)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1912 June 17; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1912 October 21; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 23)
  - Annual Meeting, 1913 January 20; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 24)
  - Quarterly Board Meeting, 1913 April 21; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 25)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1913 June 16; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 26)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1913 October 21; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 27)
  - Annual Meeting, 1914 January 19; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 28)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1914 April 20; Series 1 (Box 4B, Folder 29)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1914 June 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1914 October 19; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Special Meeting, 1914 October 23, December 12; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Annual Meeting, 1915 January 18; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1915 April 19; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1915 June 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1915 October 18; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Special Meeting, 1915 November 9-December 13-17; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Annual Meeting, 1916 January 17; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1916 April 17; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1916 June 19; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1916 October 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Memo Action and Board, 1916 November 2; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Special Meeting, 1916 December 14; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Special Meeting, 1916 December 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Annual Meeting, 1917 January 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1917 April 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1917 June 18; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1917 October 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Special Meeting, 1917 December 20; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Annual Meeting, 1918 January 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1918 April 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1918 June 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1918 October 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Special Meeting, 1918 December 12; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Annual Meeting, 1919 January 20; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Annual Meeting, 1919 January 20; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Special Meeting, 1919 February 13; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1919 April 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1919 June 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1919 October 10; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Annual Meeting, 1920 January; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Round Robin, 1920 February 17; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1920 April 23; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1920 April 23; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1920 October 29; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Annual Meeting, 1921 January 31; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1921 11 April; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 38)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1921 April 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 39)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1921 October 17; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Special Meeting, 1921 November 28; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 41)
  - Annual Report of President - Annual Meeting, 1922 January 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Annual Meeting, 1922 January 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - Adjourned Meeting, 1922 February 2; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 44)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1922 April 24; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 45)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1922 June 19; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 46)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1922 October 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 47)
  - Special Meeting, 1922 November 3, 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 48)
  - Annual Meeting, 1923 January 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 49)
  - Special Meeting, 1923 February 19; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 50)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1923 April 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 51)
  - Special Meeting, 1923 May 23; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 52)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1923 June 18; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 53)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1923 October 15; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 54)
  - Annual Meeting, 1924 January 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 55)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1924 April 21; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 56)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1924 June 16; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 57)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1924 October 20; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 58)
  - Annual Meeting, 1925 January 19; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 59)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1925 April 29; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 60)
  - Special Meeting, 1925 April 27; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 61)
  - Special Meeting, 1925 May 4-June 1; Series 1 (Box 7, Folder 62)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1925 July 6; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Special Meeting, 1925 July 31; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Memo - Meeting - Executors of W.A. Clang Estate and Committee of Trustees of Gallery, Hotel Belmont, NY City, 1925 September 9; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Special Meeting, 1925 September 14; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Quarterly Meeting, 1925 October 19; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Special Meeting, 1925 November 6; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Special Meeting, 1925 December 1; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Annual Meeting, 1926 January 18; Series 1 (Box 8, Folder 8)